(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-12T23:08:02.577790",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration now open!
ローソンへお越しのみなさん！
Everyone visiting Lawson!
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
The Lawson campaign has been confirmed!
今回はこの6人が登場！
These six members will be appearing!
詳細は3月9日公開予定！
Details scheduled to be released on March 9!
ホロライブスーパーエキスポ2026、バンダイ・BANDAI SPIRITSブースを開催！
The Bandai and BANDAI SPIRITS booth is coming to Hololive Super Expo 2026!
注目の新商品を初公開！
First public release of hot new items!
オリジナルフレームで撮影！スペシャルフォトブース！
Take photos with original frames at the special photo booth!
あなただけのカードデザイン！
Your very own card design!
ブースで限定カードがもらえる！
Get a limited card at the booth!
追加プロジェクトも公開！
Additional projects will also be revealed!
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you over and over,
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！
Come on, let's climb aboard!
ridin' on dreams
yeah！！
Yeah!!
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ (hey！！) hey！！ (hey！！)
Hey! (Hey!) Hey! (Hey!)
yeah！！
Yeah!!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a tiny dream,
想像できないような
Into something unimaginable...
想いになったんだ
It became a strong feeling,
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
Our bonds will become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
We can just blow it away!
果てない旅路を今
Along this endless journey now...
漕いでる途中に出会う困難もあるでしょう<
There will surely be difficulties we meet as we row,
それも力に変えて
But we'll turn even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
And move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't let it end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves,
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声をかけ合って
Let's hold hands and call out to each other.
地図など無い未知の世界で
In this unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行こう！
Let's keep on going!
ridin' on dreams
wow oh oh…
Wow oh oh...
hey！！ (hey！！) hey！！ (hey！！)
Hey! (Hey!) Hey! (Hey!)
yeah！！
Yeah!!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden wind
行く先乱そうとも
Tries to disrupt our path,
あの日に誓ったんだ
I made a promise on that day.
覚悟は揺るがない
My determination will not waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
I tell myself, "Get it together!"
明日への橋になる
And it becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
I have to cherish this even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
Because nothing is ever taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship...
どっから始めたらいいかもがいて
Struggling to know where to begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Little by little, we formed a circle and found...
何にも代えられない夢だ
A dream that can never be replaced.
wow oh oh oh oh oh
未完成も愛して
Love even the unfinished parts,
wow oh oh oh oh oh
想いは一つだ
Our feelings are as one,
wow oh oh oh oh oh
僅かな希望でも
Even with just a tiny bit of hope,
僕と君でずっと
You and I will always...
馬鹿にされても
Even if we are made fun of,
信じたい！
I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" isn't enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't let it end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves,
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声をかけ合って
Let's hold hands and call out to each other.
地図など無い未知の世界で
In this unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
No matter how many times we rise up,
笑い合っていたい
I want us to laugh together.
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
Come on, let's make our wishes come true together!
手を繋いで想像も超えて
Holding hands, let's surpass our imagination,
まだまだ行こう！
And keep on going!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will start shortly.
Please wait a moment.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上 照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Attention: To All Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
Attention For Visitors
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
PENLIGHT COLORS
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration Now Open!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, thank you, over and over
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
I want to tell you right now
さあ乗り込もう！ ridin' on dreams, yeah!
Come on, let's climb aboard! Ridin' on dreams, yeah!
woah, oh-oh, woah, oh-oh
hey! (hey!) hey! (hey!) yeah!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a tiny dream...
想像できないような
To something unimaginable...
想いになったんだ
It grew into this feeling,
わくわく止まらない！
My heart won't stop pounding!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
Our bonds will become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety...
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
We can easily blow it all away!
果てない旅路を今
Along this endless journey now...
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう//漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
There will probably be difficulties as we row.
それも力に変えて
But we'll turn even those into strength,
一緒に進むんだよ！
And move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there!
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too!
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, because meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行こう！ ridin' on dreams
Let's keep going! Ridin' on dreams!
woah, oh-oh, woah, oh-oh
hey! (hey!) hey! (hey!) yeah!
急な風が僕らの
Even if sudden winds...
行く先乱そうとも
Try to disrupt our path,
あの日に誓ったんだ
We made a vow on that day,
覚悟は揺るがない
Our resolve will never waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
The pressure of "I have to do this right"...
明日への橋になる
Becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
Because nothing can be taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small boat...
どっから始めたらいいか もがいて
Struggling with where we should begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
Little by little, forming a circle, we found it:
何にも代えられない夢だ
A dream that can't be replaced by anything!
(woah) 未完成も愛して
(Woah) Loving even our incomplete selves,
(woah) 想いは一つだ
(Woah) Our feelings are one.
(woah) 僅かな希望でも
(Woah) Even with just a tiny sliver of hope,
僕と君でずっと
You and I, forever...
馬鹿にされても信じたい！
We want to believe, even if they laugh at us!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" is not enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing!
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there!
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves too!
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to keep shining in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, because meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands, calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
In an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから！
Because we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone!
何度でも
No matter how many times...
立ち上がってさ
We will stand back up,
笑い合っていたい
And laugh together.
願いだって
Even our wishes...
みんなで、さあ！
Let's achieve them together, come on!
宝鐘海賊団
Houshou Pirates
撃ち抜いて
Shoot me!
リハーサルしてます
We are rehearsing!
あじまる
Ajimaru!
これが星街再演サインぬい!!!!!!
This is Suisei's signed re-performance plush!!!!!!
ローチケ当たったので、、、解散かも？
Since I won the Lawson Ticket... we might dissolve?
声出せ!!
Make some noise!!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
マリン船長 400万人おめでとう
Congratulations Captain Marine on 4 million subscribers!
落選
残念ながら今回はチケットをご用意することができませんでした
Unsuccessful
Unfortunately, we were unable to prepare tickets this time.
今月も天才
A genius this month as well
声出しして行くぞ!!
Let's make some noise!!
森カリオペ推し!
Mori Calliope Fan!
あしたは月曜日
Tomorrow is Monday
シルベ最高
Silve is the best!
ロボ子さん
Robocosan
星街すいせい
Hoshimachi Suisei
アキ・ローゼンタール
Aki Rosenthal
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
常闇トワ
Tokoyami Towa
ムーナ・ホシノヴァ
Moona Hoshinova
アーニャ・メルフィッサ
Anya Melfissa
カエラ・コヴァルスキア
Kaela Kovalskia
森カリオペ
Mori Calliope
オーロ・クロニー
Ouro Kronii
古石ビジュー
Koseki Bijou
ネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト
Nerissa Ravencroft
音乃瀬奏
Otonose Kanade
一条莉々華
Ichijou Ririka
儒烏風亭らでん
Juufuutei Raden
轟はじめ
Todoroki Hajime
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉 届け
Let our layered harmonies reach you...
Yeah!!
お互い同士描いては
As we painted each other's portraits,
いけないと笑ってた
we laughed, saying it was silly.
未来予想 あの日の続きをみよう
Our future prediction, let's see the continuation of that day.
手と手繋いで 風も着こなして
Hand in hand, styling even the wind,
扉を叩いて 進んでいくよ
knocking on doors, we'll keep moving forward.
どんなこともきっと一緒なら乗り越えていける
Surely we can overcome anything if we're together.
La la la la, la la la la
鳴り止まない 希望のメロディ ほら
Look, a melody of hope that never stops ringing.
La la la la, la la la la
聴こえてる (聴こえてる) 歌
Can you hear it? (I can hear it) Our song!
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmonies and layered words
鮮やかな日々の向こう
beyond the vibrant days.
いつでも君と
Always with you,
彩るストーリー
coloring our story.
ハーモニー 重ね進んだ旅が
Our journey of layered harmonies
空へ 駆け抜けていく
runs through to the sky,
きらめきに乗せて
carried on the sparkle,
あなたへ届け
let it reach you...
メロディ どこまでも
a melody going on forever.
曲げられないことを信じ
Believing in what cannot be bent,
ひとりじゃないよって深呼吸
take a deep breath and remember you're not alone.
痛いくらい楽しむ魔法の言葉
A magic word to enjoy to the point of hurting.
一息ついて 遠くを眺めて
Taking a breath, looking into the distance,
また君を知って 新たな旅に
knowing you more, onto a new journey.
ちょっと勇気出して 明い日へ飛び込んでいけ (明日へ飛び込んでいけ)
Gather some courage and dive into tomorrow!
La la la la, la la la la
降り積もる 道標は ほら
Look, the guideposts are piling up.
La la la la, la la la la
覚えている...
Remembering...
Harmony 手を伸ばしたら 足跡に虹がかかる
Harmony... when I reach out my hand, a rainbow forms on our footsteps.
君と晴れる 満ちてくステージ
Clearing up with you on the filling stage.
Heartbeat 記した場所へ 運ぶ約束を
Bringing the promise to the place we marked with our heartbeat.
輝きにのせて 世界へ 響け メロディ いつまでも
Carried by the brightness, let the melody ring out to the world forever.
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That step I took with you, that very moment...
宝物だって 胸を張る今
...now I can proudly say it is my treasure.
歩いて 話して 泣いて 笑っていくんだ
Walking, talking, crying, and laughing, we go on...
色褪せないまま
...never fading away.
混ざり合う僕らの声 ほら
Our voices mixing together, look...
聞こえてる
...I can hear them.
歌おう
Let's sing.
Harmony 重ねたことが 鮮やかな日々の向こう
Overlapping harmony leads us beyond those vivid days...
連れていく 君と彩るストーリー
...carrying us forward into a story colored with you.
Heartbeat 結んだ夢が 空へ駆けていく
Our dreams tied by our heartbeat run towards the sky...
煌めきにのせて あなたへ
...carried on the sparkle, to you,
世界へ 響け
letting it echo to the world,
愛を メロディ どこまでも
the melody of love, endlessly.
Parade Parade Parade 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, we're going to shine!
呼び合う声を合図に
With our calling voices as the signal,
Parade Parade Parade 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade, let's go search for it,
スタートは何度だって
our start can be made anytime, over and over.
一人きり 続く坂
On the endless slope all by myself,
ただ 始まりだけを信じた
I just believed in the beginning.
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit far away in the darkness,
それは 眩しすぎた名前
was a name that was far too dazzling,
それは 優しすぎる声
and a voice that was far too kind.
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
Reaching out my hand to get even closer,
思いがけず 結び合った
our unexpected feelings bound together.
ほら 今 迷いはない 物語になった
Look, now there's no hesitation, it has become a story!
Parade Parade Parade 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, we're going to shine!
悔しさも 愛おしさも 連れておいで
Bring along your frustrations and your dearest moments.
乗せて 夢 晴れ 飛び立てるさ
With our dreams and clear skies, we can fly!
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer becomes the light,
終わりのない予感
an endless premonition.
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
I can hold my head high for having found you.
ここから これから Our Bright Parade
From here on, from now on, Our Bright Parade!
頼りない予感も
Even those unreliable premonitions,
歌う 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
I will sing of them, there's nothing to be ashamed of.
誰も解けない 愛おしき日々
These precious days that no one can break apart,
いつかまた会おう おまじない
an incantation to meet again someday.
あの日 ゼロから始まったストーリー
The story that started from zero on that day...
数えきれないことばかり
...so many things we cannot count,
数えるような想いじゃないさ
they aren't feelings that can be simply counted.
ほら 今 僕らを 一つ 繋ぐよ
Look, now, tying us together as one!
Parade Parade Parade 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's so beautiful!
許し合える 刹那の夜は 煌めく
The night of fleeting forgiveness sparkles.
Parade Parade Parade また 遠い空
Parade, parade, parade, again to the distant sky,
相応しい 旅路を行こう
let's go on a journey worthy of us.
君と在ることさ
is being with you,
君と在ることなんだ
is simply being with you.
ただいまを聞けば
When you say "I'm home,"
おかえりって叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that only natural?
Parade, Parade, Parade！ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's time to take the stage
暗がりを 満たすのは 君 だ 僕 だ ！
We are the ones who fill the darkness... you and I!
Parade, Parade, Parade！ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! It's time to take the stage
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
When disappointment gets in your way, love will shine, keeping you safe
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Feel the wind and wishes, your wings will take you high
ささやかな祈りは光 終わりなき兆し
These silent prayers will become our light, guiding us on an endless flight
君と 飛び込んでゆく 素敵な スタート さ
Here I am ready to dive into a beautiful start with you
ここから これから Our Bright Parade, Parade！
Starting from here, starting right now, Our Bright Parade, Parade!
Our Bright Parade, Parade！
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
それでは、それでは、ステージ４、スタートです！
And now, and now, Stage 4 is starting!
愛したって 愛したって
Even if I love you, even if I love you,
もう何も伝わらなくて
Nothing gets through to you anymore.
愛してって叫んだって
Even if I scream that I love you,
ホロライブ 4th Fes おかわり！最後のステージだー！
hololive 4th Fes Okawari! It's the final stage!
あの子とは違うんだって
You said you're different from that girl
勘違いって言ってんのに
And that it was all a misunderstanding
聞く耳もありゃしませんで
But you won't even listen to me
どうやって伝えたって
No matter how I try to tell you,
ひとつだって刺さんなくてさ
Not a single word gets through to you.
まるで アタシは 幽霊
It's like I'm a ghost.
あの頃は良かったね
Things were so good back then,
忘れられない
I can't forget them.
返事してくれなきゃ嫌だ
I hate it if you don't reply to me.
うらめしや
Curse you!
タタリのウォーーアイニー！
A curse of Wo Ai Ni!
バカみたい アタシ ダンス！ダンス！
I'm dancing like a fool! Dance! Dance!
踊り明かせ
Let's dance the night away
アナタにフォーリンラブ
I'm falling in love with you
成仏しそう
I feel like passing on,
でも ダンス！ダンス！
But dance! Dance!
なんで無視すんねん
Why are you ignoring me?
そばにいるのに
Even though I'm right beside you,
心は遠く
Your heart is so far away.
でも愛してる
But I still love you.
泣いたって泣いたって
Even if I cry, even if I cry,
もうキミは依然ブレんね
You still won't budge at all.
あーもうわかった
Ah, I get it now.
わかったわかっちゃったね
I get it, I totally get it.
キミもおばけになっちゃえば
If you became a ghost too,
笑ってくれるね！<,s:
You'd smile for me, wouldn't you?!
地獄のパーティータイム
Hell's party time!
白黒関係ない ダンス！ダンス！
Black or white doesn't matter, dance! Dance!
忘れさせて
Let me forget it all,
悲しさミラーボール
The sadness mirror ball.
踊りましょう
Let us dance,
ほら ダンス！ダンス！
Come on, dance! Dance!
いつまで無視すんねん
How long are you going to ignore me?
タタリのウォーーアイニー！
A curse of Wo Ai Ni!
どっかから聞こえる ダンス！ダンス！
I hear it from somewhere, dance! Dance!
疲れてきた
I'm getting tired now,
アタシも寝るね
So I'm going to sleep too.
成仏しよう
Let's pass on,
ほら ダンス！ダンス！
Come on, dance! Dance!
お揃いでイイね
It's nice that we're matching.
やっと逢えたね
We finally met,
これからずっと
From now on, forever,
二人で永遠に
Just the two of us, eternally...
ダンス！ダンス！愛してるダンス！
Dance! Dance! I love you, dance!
ダンス！ダンス！恋のステッピング！
Dance! Dance! The stepping of love!
ダンス！ダンス！魅惑のターン！
Dance! Dance! The charming turn!
ダンス！ダンス！
Dance! Dance!
ずっと愛してる
I will love you forever.
それ「my god」
...That's "my god"
アイウォンチュー ウォンチュー IQが下がっていく感じ
I want you, want you, feeling my IQ drop away
まだ満たされない
Still not satisfied
どれも哀を模したTRUE
All mimicking sorrow, TRUE
おー！逃がさんぞ！
Oh! I won't let you escape!
この爪は、吾輩の…待て！はい！
These claws are mine... Wait! Yes!
今すぐ、邪魔してちゅっちゅっちゅってしちゃうよ！
I'm going to get in your way right now and kiss you!
待っててね！
Wait for me, okay?!
イエス！もう破裂しちゃう！
Yes! I'm about to burst!
抑えきれないの
I can't contain it,
わたしのハートがドクドクドクドクしている
my heart is beating thumpty-thump.
潤んだ瞳
Moist eyes,
困ったくちびる
troubled lips,
悪戯な笑顔
and a mischievous smile.
もう止まらないの
I can't stop it anymore,
わたしの中の何かがズズズズ…ぎゅー！
something inside me is surging... Squeeze!
溢れ出しちゃう
It's about to overflow!
はーっ！
Haa!
あたまのてっぺんまでビリビリ感じちゃう
I feel it tingling all the way to the top of my head!
あちち、しゃかりきよ、子猫ちゃん
Hot, hot! Give it your all, little kitten!
隠れてないでよ顔見せて
Don't hide from me, let me see your face.
風通し良好
Well-ventilated,
100%！出力最大！
100%! Maximum output!
お！
Oh!
見つけた！
Found you!
胸がキュンキュン 愛はとまらないの
My heart is throbbing, my love won't stop!
しゅき しゅき だいしゅき marry me
I love, love, love you, marry me!
わたしだけのお姫様
My very own princess,
もう離さない ずっと
I'll never let you go, forever!
教会で式を挙げましょう
Let's have our wedding in a church,
神様だって困っちゃう
even God would be at a loss!
思い立ったのでいっちゃおう
Since we've decided, let's go on our...
ハネムーン チュッ
honeymoon! Chu!
お嫁、ハニー チュッ
My bride, honey! Chu!
おかえりなさいのちゅーは？
Where is my welcome home kiss?
ちゅっ、ちゅっ
Chu, chu!
さて、ご飯にしようかな？
Now, should we have dinner?
お風呂にしようかな？
Should we take a bath?
それとも、わ・た・し？
Or maybe... me?
今日はこれから二人で楽しいショッピングデート！
Today, we're going on a fun shopping date together!
ダーリン、もう準備できてる？
Darling, are you ready yet?
ダーリン？
Darling?
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
もしかして、ラプラスとかくれんぼしたいのかな？
Are you trying to play hide-and-seek with Laplus?
テーブルの下？ クローゼットの中かな？
Under the table? Inside the closet?
よーし、ラプラス、本気出しちゃうぞー！
Alright, Laplus is going to get serious now!
100%！
100%!
甘い鼓動のリズム
The rhythm of a sweet heartbeat,
赤い糸で二人繋がっているの ハートがビンビン
we are connected by a red thread, my heart is tingling!
こっち向いて、ダーリン
Look over here, darling.
あはははは！
Ahahaha!
見つけた！
Found you!
恋はもう誰にも止められないの
No one can stop our love anymore!
しゅき しゅき だいしゅき marry me
I love, love, love you, marry me!
二人だけの愛の巣から
From our very own love nest,
もう逃がさない ずっと
I'll never let you escape, forever!
永遠の愛を誓いましょう
Let's vow our eternal love,
神様サインをくれるよ
God will give us a sign!
我慢できない 早く
I can't wait, hurry,
いっちゃおう Welcome to heaven
let's go, Welcome to heaven!
檻の中に
Inside the cage,
囚われて
imprisoned,
凍りついた my love
my frozen love.
しゅわしゅわしゅわ baby
Shuwa shuwa shuwa baby
健やかなるときも、病めるときも
In sickness and in health,
命ある限り、ラブラブちゅっちゅすることを誓います！
as long as we live, I vow to love and kiss you!
世界で一番、愛してるよ
I love you more than anyone in the world.
ベイビー、もうわたしを一人にしないで
Baby, don't leave me alone anymore,
あなた、あなたがいないとダメなの
I can't do anything without you...
寂しがり屋なわたしの
of my lonely self,
そばにいて、ずっと
stay by my side, forever!
みんなのことも愛してるよー！
I love all of you too!
胸がキュンキュン 愛はとまらないの
My heart is throbbing, my love won't stop!
しゅき しゅき だいしゅき marry me
I love, love, love you, marry me!
わたしだけのお姫様
My very own princess,
もう離さない ずっと
I'll never let you go, forever!
教会で式を挙げましょう
Let's have our wedding in a church,
神様だって困っちゃう
even God would be at a loss!
思い立ったのでいっちゃおう
Since we've decided, let's go on our...
ハネムーン チュッ
honeymoon! Chu!
お嫁、ハニー
My bride, honey!
ありがとう、ダーリン！
Thank you, darling!
チュッ！
Chu!
あ！マリンちみめっちゃちゅーきー！
Ah! I love Marine's crew so much!
ないない足りないないない
No, no, not enough, no, no, no!
ないない船ないないない
No, no, no ship, no, no, no!
背に腹は代えられない
Desperate times call for desperate measures,
マネーにオールバイ
buying it all with money!
円たらポンドユーロ マネーにシュキシュキ
Yen, pound, euro, loving money!
ルピーアリラウォン元と オンマネーバー
Rupee, lira, won, yuan... Om Mani Ba!
寄ってらっしゃいなったら
Come on over!
おいでなしゃっちょ様
Welcome, clients!
お宝売りますえら
Treasures are on sale!
レッツゴー・オークション！
Let's go auction!
ドクロの旗
Skull flag!
オンボロパーカー
Tattered hoodie!
フリフリの眼帯は 使用済み！
Frilly eyepatch is... used!
ハウマッチ？
How much?
はい 100万円！
Yes, 1 million yen!
からの？
And then?
はい 1億円！
Yes, 100 million yen!
からの？
And then?
はい 1兆円！
Yes, 1 trillion yen!
もうひと超え♡ ハウマッチ？
Just a bit more! How much?
はい 1京円！
Yes, 1 quadrillion yen!
からの？
And then?
はい 2京円！
Yes, 2 quadrillion yen!
はい 3無量大数！
Yes, 3 undecillion!
ぶっ飛んで 5000兆！
Blowing past that... 5,000 trillion!
欲しいの欲しいのマネーマネー 助けて欲しいのシャイシャイシャイ
I want it, I want it, money, money! Help me, I'm shy, shy, shy!
脱出よ オンマネーバー
Escape now, Om Mani Ba!
バレバレバレバレバレバレバイレ
Exposed, exposed, exposed, expo-auction!
売り出せやお宝トパパパパッパパ
Put the treasures up for sale, pa-pa-pa-pa!
サインでもちゅき 恋 承認行為
Love even with just an autograph, act of validation!
なんてね
Just kidding!
だらだら欲望カードだされ
Sloppily showing off my desire card,
ベラベラポンドを見出され
spilling pounds babbling,
しょうきどきどききき
sanity thumping, thumping, thumping,
ぐるぐる世界が回わされて
the world is spinning around!
スーパーチャイニングな夜はハッピーサマー
Super shining night, happy summer,
いざハマー
now, hammer time!
コングラチュレーション！
Congratulations!
円たらポンドユーロ マニーにシュキシュキ
Yen, pound, euro, loving money!
ルピーアリラウォン元と オンマネーバー
Rupee, lira, won, yuan... Om Mani Ba!
ドルかベストたら アレアルマルクシリング
If dollars are best, then real, mark, shilling,
タイバーツと名金銀銅 オンマネーバー
Thai baht, and famous gold, silver, copper! Om Mani Ba!
お宝売って 入金あって お船を買って ハッピーピー
Selling treasure, getting paid, buying a ship, happy-py!
出航して 嵐に逢って バッタンQ
Sailing out, meeting a storm, bam, knocked flat!
何もかも失いで 口座見て あとの祭りか 攻略させて
Losing everything, checking the account, too late now, let me conquer!
大発見！ これは！ マリンが命名する
Great discovery! This is... Marine's naming of...
愛の地球
Earth of love!
ワンちゃんの防具
Doggy's armor!
よだれ拭く布
Drool wipe!
まだまだ足りない！
Still not enough!
ヌギタテブーツ
Freshly removed boots!
サービスサービス
Service, service!
まんまるぼっちのぎゅっ抱っこ
A tight hug for a lonely round-one!
ハウマッチ？
How much?
はい 100万円！
Yes, 1 million yen!
からの？
And then?
はい 1億円！
Yes, 100 million yen!
からの？
And then?
はい 1兆円！
Yes, 1 trillion yen!
もうひと超え♡ ハウマッチ？
Just a bit more! How much?
はい 1京円！
Yes, 1 quadrillion yen!
からの？
And then?
はい 2京円！
Yes, 2 quadrillion yen!
からの？
And then?
はい 3無量大数！
Yes, 3 undecillion!
ぶっ飛んで 5000兆！
Blowing past that... 5,000 trillion!
ドキドキして ルージュ
Heart pounding, rouge...
マリン、いきますよ〜！
Marine, here I go!
無罪！ 無罪！ 美少女無罪！
Innocent! Innocent! Beautiful girls are innocent!
マリン！ マリン！ マリンは無罪！
Marine! Marine! Marine is innocent!
やっぱキラキラもっとクラクラ
As expected, sparkling and dizzier!
ねえ、言ったよね？
Hey, you said it, right?
年齢なんて関係ないってさ
That age doesn't matter!
そういう面倒くさいのも
And that you would love me...
含めて愛してくれるって
including all those annoying parts!
ねえねえ、言ったよね？言ってない？
Hey, hey, you said it, right? You didn't?
ふーん、そういうこと言うんだ
Hmph, so that's how it is...
ちなみにこの船では
By the way, on this ship,
美少女無罪が適用されますけど？
the "beautiful girl is innocent" rule applies!
まかせて 魔法では若返り
Leave it to me! Rejuvenating with magic,
ヒミツの素顔はキミにだけ
my secret real face is only for you,
トクベツですよ〜？
it's special, okay?
あぁ... アタシ厄介よ
Ah... I'm troublesome.
あぁ... 港なんかじゃ はしゃげないわ 近頃はね
Ah... at a place like a port, I can't frolic lately.
宝の島にしてほしい気分
I feel like making it a treasure island.
出航ー！
Set sail!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice! Beautiful girls are innocent!
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Sailing ahead to be your number one!
本当は自信ないけど頑張っちゃう
I'm not really confident, but I'll do my best!
アホイ！
Ahoy!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun!
きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurunrun!
恋する気持ち 17歳
Loving feelings, 17 years old!
0時になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
It's becoming midnight, time for adults!
やっぱキラキラもっとクラクラ
As expected, sparkling and dizzier!
ドキドキして ルージュ
Heart pounding, rouge...
あぁ、お許しくだた〜い！
Ah, please forgive me!
このマリンの......
This Marine's...
魅力！ 魔力！ 不可抗力！
Charm! Magic! Force majeure!
──"罪な女"ね？
──Such a "sinful woman", right?
離さないで つかまっていて
Don't let go, hold on tight,
世界の広さ 見せてあげるから
because I'll show you how wide the world is!
出航ー！
Set sail!
キュートは正義 美少女無罪
Cute is justice! Beautiful girls are innocent!
キミの一番目指してヨーソロー！
Sailing ahead to be your number one!
冗談も大好きだけど真剣よ
I love jokes, but I'm serious!
アホイ！
Ahoy!
きゅっきゅっきゅるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurun!
きゅっきゅっきゅるんるん
Kyu-kyu-kyurunrun!
恋する気持ち 17歳
Loving feelings, 17 years old!
0時になっちゃうわ オトナの時間
It's becoming midnight, time for adults!
やっぱキラキラもっとクラクラ
As expected, sparkling and dizzier!
ドキドキして ルージュ
Heart pounding, rouge...
まだ早い♡
It's still too early!
マリンじゃなくて
It's not "Marine,"
マリン船長だろぉん！？
it's Captain Marine, right?!
音乃瀬奏
Kanade Otonose
一条莉々華
Ririka Ichijou
儒烏風亭らでん
Raden Juufuutei
轟はじめ
Hajime Todoroki
ReGLOSS
紙細工の花びらを
A paper flower's petal...
ある人は「美しい」と呟いた
...someone whispered that it was beautiful.
この地球の横顔は
How does the profile of this Earth...
どう見えてる？ 君の世界では
...look to you in your world?
現実をさかさまにして
Turning reality upside down,
失いそうなものだけ振り落とした
I shook off only the things I was about to lose.
手のひらで拾い上げようとしたら
When I tried to scoop them up in my palms,
指の隙間 すり抜けて消えてった
they slipped through my fingers and disappeared.
形あるものだけがすべてじゃないけれど
Although physical things aren't everything...
形あるものが葛藤してでも欲しいよ
...I still want them, even if it means struggling.
この世界を 変えることは
Changing this world...
きっと出来ないけれど
...is surely something I cannot do,
君の中の世界なら
but if it's the world inside of you,
変えられるはず
I should be able to change it.
振り向いて 咲いてみせて 枯れて
Turn around, show me your bloom, and wither.
何一つ欠かせないから
Because not a single piece can be spared.
最後に君が笑ってくれれば
In the end, if you would just smile for me,
もうそれだけでいい
then that alone is enough.
言葉の綾 紡ぐ人と
Those who spin figures of speech,
優しさを編む人
and those who weave kindness,
それぞれの正義を分かってあげたい
I want to understand each of their forms of justice.
絡まった矛盾と辻褄合わせ
Tangled contradictions and rationalizations...
そんな切なさを抱え 今日を生きた
holding such sorrow, I lived through today.
分け合った灯り
The light we shared...
隣から隣へ
...passes from one hand to another,
やがて一つに 夜の帳へ
eventually becoming one in the curtain of night.
息を吹き込んだ
I breathed life into it...
君とじゃなきゃダメなんだ
...because it has to be with you.
このまま寝てしまうには
もったいない程
Just going to sleep like this...
優しさにくるまった
...would be such a waste,
夜だった
in this night wrapped...
発進力 浮かび上がった
Propulsive force, emerging...
夢の輪郭
...the silhouette of dreams.
それは確かに愛だった
That was certainly love.
月が見守る航路
Along the path watched over by the moon,
一瞬を立ち止めて
halting for a single instant,
きらめく星
a glittering star.
色や形 温度や響き
Colors and shapes, temperatures and echoes,
何もかも違う僕らだけど
though we are different in every way,
きっと最後には
surely in the end,
同じ手で繋がって
we'll connect with the same hands.
この世界を
Changing this world...
変えることはきっと出来ないけれど
...is surely something I cannot do,
君の中の世界なら
but if it's the world inside of you,
変えられるはず
I should be able to change it.
振り向いて 咲いてみせて 枯れて
Turn around, show me your bloom, and wither.
何一つ欠かせないから
Because not a single piece can be spared.
最後に君が笑ってくれれば
In the end, if you would just smile for me,
もうそれだけでいい
then that alone is enough.
みんな聴いてくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for listening!
楽しんでくれましたか？
Did you all enjoy it?
ステージ4、まだまだ続きます！
Stage 4 is still going strong!
盛り上がっていってください！
Keep the excitement going!
ただいま！
We're back!
ホロフェス ステージ4、始まりました！
HoloFes Stage 4 has officially begun!
エキスポとフェス、最終日だよ！
It's the final day of EXPO and Fes!
まだまだいけるよね！
You can still keep going, right?!
ちょっとね、今、歌って踊ったばっかりで、疲れて…
To be honest, we just finished singing and dancing, so we're tired...
ないです！まだまだ元気バリバリあります！
...NOT! We've still got tons of energy left!
すごい元気だね！
You're so energetic!
でも、こんなにもさ、たくさんの声援を浴びたらさ、もうパワーもらっちゃうよね！
But showering in so much cheering like this, of course we'd get energized!
本当にさ！でも、まだまだステージは続いていきますので、皆さん、右肩上がりで…
Exactly! But the stage is still continuing, so everyone, keep rising higher...
もっとデカい声で！
...with even louder voices!
わっさわっさね！
Wassawassa!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃ、ちょっと自己紹介からさせていただきます！
Well then, let's start with our introductions!
はい！
Yes!
可愛いポジティブ、ギガ熱！
Cute, positive, giga-hot!
めっちゃ嬉しい！ホロライブDEV_IS ReGLOSSの一条莉々華だよ！こんりり！
I'm so happy! It's Ichijou Ririka from hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS! Konriri!
わあ、めっちゃ嬉しい！
Wow, I'm so happy!
そして！
And!
ホロライブDEV_IS所属、ReGLOSSの文化担当、儒烏風亭らでんです！こんらでん！
From hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS, I'm the culture representative, Juufuutei Raden! Konraden!
なに、なに、なに？ええー？こんらでん！
What was that? Huh? Konraden!
もうさっきまではさ、「らでん氏、ちょっとドキドキする」って言ってたのに！
Just a moment ago you were saying, "Raden-shi is a bit nervous"!
うつった、うつった！
It rubbed off, it rubbed off!
皆さん、楽しんでますか？！
Everyone, are you having fun?!
ペンライトも莉々華殿の色にしてくれてる！
They've even changed their penlights to Ririka-den's color!
ねえ、すごい！ありがとう！
Wow, amazing! Thank you!
はい、ということで...
Yes, so...
もうすでに何曲か、みんなにね、お披露目できたと思うんですけれども、
We've already been able to perform a few songs for everyone,
はい！
Yes!
今回ちょっとね、フェスのテーマとして「Ridin' on Dreams」ということで、
This time, with the festival theme being "Ridin' on Dreams,"
ステージとして皆さんのお客さんのね、架け橋の形が、トロッコとして、ね、出てきました！
the bridge between the stage and you, the audience, appeared as trolleys!
すごい！近かったよね！
Amazing! We were so close!
それね、私たちも乗らせてもらったんですけど、もう本当に、みんなのね、笑顔が、嬉しそうな顔が見えました！
We got to ride on them too, and we could really see everyone's smiles and happy faces!
見えてたよ！めっちゃ見えてたよ！顔とか持ってるグッズとか！最高！
We could see you! We could see you so well! Your faces and the merch you were holding! The best!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
もうね、なんか、せっかくMC務めさせていただいたから、なんかやりたいことあるんじゃないの？
Since we got this chance to do the MC, isn't there something you want to do?
あれ！あれ！
Oh, that! That!
社長、何やりたい？
President, what do you want to do?
一番最初の全体曲の時から、なんかみんなのね、掛け声とかペンライトとかが、もうぶわぁーって！
Since the very first group song, everyone's cheers and penlights were like, WHOOSH!
ぶわぁーって嬉しそうにきて、
They came at us so wonderfully,
そうだよね。
That's true.
ちょっとそれを、このMC中にもちょっとやりたいんですけど、いいですか？！
I want to do a bit of that during this MC too, is that okay?!
いいですか？！
Is that okay?!
やった！じゃ、莉々華は、ペンライトを使って、ちょっとみんなと交流したいです！いいですか？皆さん、ペンライトの準備は？！
Yay! Then, Ririka wants to use the penlights to interact with everyone! Is that okay? Everyone, are your penlights ready?!
社長の色は分かるよね？！
You know the President's color, right?!
じゃ、ちょっと全部を、濃いピンク！薄いピンクじゃないですよ、莉々華の濃いピンクにしてみてらってもいいですか？！
Then, could you make them all deep pink? Not light pink! Ririka's deep pink, is that okay?!
もう出来てるよ！すごい！すごい！
They're already doing it! Amazing! Amazing!
お花畑みたい！
It's like a flower field!
じゃ、次は、らでんのカラーであるイエローにしてもらってもいいですか？！
Then next, could you make them Raden's color, yellow?!
めっちゃ黄色にしてくれるの？！
Are you going to make them all yellow?!
ありがとう！最高！
Thank you! The best!
じゃ、次は、莉々華がピンクって言ったらピンク、黄色って言ったら黄色にしてね！
Next, when Ririka says pink, make it pink, and when I say yellow, make it yellow!
出来るかな？！
Can you do it?!
出来るかな？急ぐね！
Can they do it? It's fast!
あ、ピンクになってる！
Ah, they're turning pink!
すごい！どんどん変わってる、どんどん変わってる！
Amazing! They're changing more and more, changing more and more!
頑張って！
Do your best!
ありがとう！ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
じゃ、好きな色！
Then, your favorite color!
ねえすごい、お花畑みたい！ありがとうございます、とっても嬉しそうです。
Wow, it really looks like a flower field! Thank you so much, I'm so happy.
じゃ、らでんは何やりたい？
Then, what does Raden want to do?
え、らでんはもう分かってると思うけど...
Well, I think you already know what Raden wants...
らでんがちょっとこのDay 3のMCとして出たということは...
The fact that Raden is here as the Day 3 MC means...
今日は何曜日だったかな？！
What day of the week was it today?!
みんな知ってるよね、らでんが「明日は！」って言ったら、皆さんもう生まれてきて一番のでっかい声で「月曜日！」って叫んでくださいね、いいですか？！
Everyone knows, right? When Raden says, "Tomorrow is...", please shout "Monday!" with the loudest voice of your life, okay?!
いやぁー！
Nooo!
月曜日ですよ！行きますよ！
It's Monday! Here we go!
明日は？！
Tomorrow is?!
月曜日！！！
Monday!!!
月曜日！最高！ありがとう！
Monday! The best! Thank you!
いや、でも明日が月曜日でもね、そんな疲れも吹っ飛ぶぐらい、今日は最高のパフォーマンスをみんなに届けていきますので、皆さんまだまだ...
Well, even if tomorrow is Monday, we're going to deliver the best performance to blow away that exhaustion today, so everyone...
盛り上がっていきますよー！
Let's keep this energy going!
いきますよー！
Let's go!
いいねー！
Nice!
もっといけるよねー！
You can do even better, right?
まだまだいけるよねー！
You can still do more, right?
いけるいける！
Yeah, you can!
最高！
Awesome!
はい！ということで、あのね
Okay! So, you see...
今回現地に来てくださっているみんなと
everyone who came to the venue today...
配信で見てくださっているみんなも
and everyone watching the stream, too...
そう、コメントも見えてますからね！
That's right, we can see your comments, too!
見えておりますので！
Yes, we can see them!
配信のみんなは、ハッシュタグ
For those watching the stream, please use the hashtag...
#ホロライブフェスエキスポ26デイ3
#hololiveFesExpo26Day3
と、たくさんポストしてくれたら嬉しいです！
and post a lot! We'd love it if you did!
嬉しいです！
We'd love it!
いぇーい！
Yay!
そして、そして！
And, and!
楽しいお知らせがあるんですけど！
We have some exciting news!
楽しいお知らせ？
Exciting news?
何？何？
What is it? What?
YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方は、ここまでとなります！
For those watching on YouTube and TikTok, this is where it ends!
えええー！どうしよう！
Oh no! What should we do!
はい、でもね、よかったら皆さん
But yes, if you'd like, everyone...
まだまだ楽しいライブは続きますので
the fun concert will still continue,
引き続き観てもらえると嬉しいです！
so we'd be happy if you keep watching!
はい！いっぱい声出して応援してね！
Yes! Raise your voices and cheer for us!
応援してください！
Please cheer for us!
それではですね、ちょっと次の曲に入りたいと思いますので
Now, we'd like to move on to the next song...
「せーの」って言ったら、みんなで
so when I say "Ready, set...",
今回のね、テーマである
everyone, please shout the theme of this event,
「Ridin' on Dreams」と叫んでもらえたら嬉しいです！
"Ridin' on Dreams"! We'd love that!
いいですか？
Are you ready?
おっけー！
Okay!
それじゃあ行くよ！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
Ridin' on Dreams!
引き続き楽しんでいってねー！
Keep having fun!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[On-screen text: The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.]
無料パートは終了いたしました！
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.